<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyQuiz</string>
    <string name="quizzz">Quizzz</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="text" translatable="false"></string>

    <string-array name="title_story">

        <item>HairCut Every Two Weeks </item>
        <item>Grab Your Umbrellas </item>
        <item>Raising the Kids Right </item>
        <item>Loves To Ride Motorcycle </item>
        <item>Everyone Loves Yellow Banana </item>
        <item>Boy Defends his Sister </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="detailed_story">

        <item>
              It was time for a haircut. Lenny didnt even have to look in the mirror. Even though he was going bald, he knew that he needed to cut his hair every two weeks.
            He had a tongue of hair on the top of his head. His hair was thinning at the crown. He still had plenty of hair on the sides and back. It was what they call salt and pepper, a mixture of gray hair and dark brown hair. It was only a few years, he figured, until the salt and pepper became just salt.

He never let his hair grow for more than two weeks. The longer it got, the worse it looked, he thought.

He spread a newspaper over the bathroom sink so that no hair went down the drain. He plugged in the clippers and started cutting his hair. He started at the back of his head, went to the sides, and finished on the top. Every minute or so, he had to clean the hair out of the blades with an old toothbrush.

Finished, he picked up a hand mirror to check out the back of his head. Everything looked okay. He carried the newspaper back out to the kitchen and shook the hair clippings into the trash can. Then he took a shower.
        </item>

        <item>It looked like rain. The sky was gray. It was almost noon, but the sun was hidden by a gray blanket. It was cool. There were no birds flying anywhere. A couple of birds sat on the telephone wire. Bob was standing outside talking to Bill. They both had their hands in their pockets. They knew that it was probably going to rain shortly. A sudden breeze blew some leaves off a tree onto the sidewalk.

A young woman wearing a dark blue coat and jeans walked by. She was walking a small dog. It was pure white, and pretty. It sniffed at a tree trunk. The woman waited patiently. Finally, the dog lifted its leg.

Bob said that he liked the rain. It was a nice change from the usual hot Los Angeles weather. And the plants could always use the extra water. Bill said the only thing he didnt like about rain was that all the motor oil on the streets would get washed into the ocean, and so would all the trash.

But that never stops the surfers, Bob said. They dont seem to care whats in the water, as long as there are waves to surf on.
        </item>



        <item>
        Louise and Neil had been dating for three years. She was 40, and he was 50. They wanted to get married and have two kids as soon as possible, but there was a problem. They disagreed on how they would raise their kids.

Because Louise had a high‐paying job, Neil could stay home and raise the kids. He looked forward to that, because he felt that he would be a great dad. First, he would teach them how to read. Then he would teach them about life. His kids were not going to waste their time reading fairy tales and watching Sesame Street. They were going to learn practical stuff, like how to use Microsoft Office and how to get a four‐year scholarship to Harvard. He wanted them to become business majors, because business is where the money is.

Louise had other plans. She wanted her kids to relax and enjoy life. She didnt want them to grow up too fast. She was the oldest child in a poor family, and her father had put her to work in the fields as soon as she turned six. Life had been hard for her. She didnt want it to be hard for her children.

Neil said not to worry. There was still plenty of time for him to figure out a way for the kids to have fun and still become happy millionaires.
        </item>



        <item>
            Jay was born to ride. Just after learning to walk, he got his first tricycle. A year later he was on a bicycle with training wheels. At the age of five he was a skilled bicyclist, able to jump off ramps and fly through the air. His father made sure he did everything safely. Jay wore a helmet, a chest pad, elbow pads, and knee pads. He fell a lot, but he was never hurt badly.

He got his first motorcycle when he was seven. His father put the motorcycle in the back of his pickup and drove Jay out to the desert almost every weekend. Jay became a skilled rider. He entered motocross races all over the county. By the time he was 15, he had won 30 races. His future looked bright.

When he was 17, Jay took his girlfriend out for a ride on his motorcycle. A truck ran a red light, and Jay and his girlfriend crashed into the side of the truck. Jay went into the hospital for three months. His girlfriend died immediately.

Jay didnt ride a motorcycle again for 10 years. Then one weekend he bought a used Kawasaki. He took it out for a test run at dusk. It felt good to ride again. He got it up to 110 miles an hour on the local freeways. A highway patrol car chased him for about ten minutes, but he finally lost it in the freeway traffic and the dark. When he got home, he was excited. That was fun, he thought.
        </item>



        <item>
            What a wonderful fruit the banana is, popular all over the world. Its three colors tell you how ripe it is. Green means go, as in go find another banana. Yellow means eat me. Brown means eat me but dont bother chewing before you swallow. The only thing that would make a banana more user friendly is if you could eat the peel. Plus, a banana is neat to eat. When you bite into it, you dont have to worry about juice squirting all over yourself and your dinner neighbors like oranges or grapefruit, for example. And its a silent food. You can chew it all you like without driving your neighbors crazy with crunching sounds like apples or carrots, for example. Finally, its easy to cut. You dont need a steak knife, you can slice it with a fork or a spoon, if you like.
       You re never too young or too old to eat bananas. Babies eat mashed bananas before their teeth grow in. Great great grandparents eat mashed bananas after their teeth fall out.

The banana is versatile. You can fry it, bake it, mash it, or eat it raw. You can slice it and put it on your breakfast cereal. At lunchtime you can snack on a raw banana, or make a peanut butter and banana sandwich, or eat a bag of dried bananas. You can add a banana to your ice cream for dessert and call it a banana split. You can order a healthful banana smoothie at your local smoothie store. On weekends you can order a banana daiquiri at your local bar or restaurant.

Here in the U.S., we get most of our bananas from Ecuador and Costa Rica, although the fruit reportedly originated in Asia. Bananas give us lots of potassium and vitamins A and C, and hardly any sodium. The price of bananas hasnt changed much over recent years they re still about 65 cents a pound, despite rising gas and labor prices. If thats too expensive, you can still get three pounds for a buck at many dollar stores.
        </item>


        <item>
            A nine year old boy defended his sister from her angry ex boyfriend yesterday. Woody Harrelson, 24, who had a house key, had hidden in the closet of the Shatner familys home waiting for his ex girlfriend Ethel, 23, to return. He attacked Ethel with a knife seconds after she arrived home. She was carrying their 11 month old baby in her arms. Woody stabbed away, not caring if he injured his baby or not. Ethel, bleeding and screaming, ran into her bedroom and put the baby into the crib. Woody followed her into the bedroom.

Curt ran into the bedroom and jumped onto Woodys back. From behind, he managed to jam his fingers into Woodys eyes. Woody yelled and dropped the knife. As Woody stumbled around rubbing his eyes, Curt grabbed the knife and plunged it twice into Woodys lower back. Woody ran out of the house. Curt held onto the knife in case Woody came back. Ethel called 911. The paramedics treated Ethels wounds and transported her to the hospital, where she is in stable condition. The baby, protected by its heavy clothing and a blanket, was unharmed. Woody has not been caught yet.

All hospitals in the area were alerted to watch for Woody, because Curt said that he got him good. In fact, said one doctor, Woody should get to a hospital as soon as possible. He might bleed to death if Curt actually punctured one of Woodys kidneys. The paramedics and police commended little Curt for his bravery. He said that it was his responsibility to protect his sister, because When Daddys not home, I m the man of the family.
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>